(Leonard:)See, this right here,
what you're doing,
(Leonard:)can you please not do that
around Sheldon's mom?
(Dr Hofstadter:)Why? Are you attracted
to her, too?
(Sheldon:)Of course not.
She's-she's just a very
sweet and God-fearing lady,
(Leonard:)and you have to be
respectful of her beliefs.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Leonard, I'm an adult.
(Dr Hofstadter:)I know how to conduct myself
around people
(Dr Hofstadter:)from different
walks of life.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Where is she from again?
(Leonard:)East Texas.
Ugh.
(Leonard:)Hey, look who's here.
Oh, Dr. Hofstadter,
it's so good to see you again.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Likewise.
I read your paper;
it was very impressive.
(Sheldon:)Oh, thank you.
(Leonard:)We just spent
two hours in traffic.
(Leonard:)Did you think to mention to me
that you liked our paper?
(Dr Hofstadter:)Of course I did, but
it's a mother's job
(Dr Hofstadter:)to make sure her child's
self-esteem is not dependent
(Dr Hofstadter:)on anyone's approval.
(Leonard:)That's so sweet,
you think I have self-esteem.
Dr. Hofstadter, I want you
to meet my mother, Mary.